Usage: faust2esp32 [options] [Faust options] <file.dsp> <file.dsp>
faust2esp32 can be used to fully program the ESP32 microncontroller and to generate DSP objects
that can be integrated into any ESP32 project. 
Additional information about this tool can be found on the Faust website: https://faust.grame.fr.
Options:
   -gramophone : generates for GRAME Gramophone
   -multi : generate for GRAME Gramophone in multi DSP mode
   -lib : generates a package containing an object compatible with any ESP32 project
   -midi : activates MIDI control
   -soundfile : when compiling a DSP using the 'soundfile' primitive, add required resources
   -main : add a 'main' entry point
   -nvoices <num> : produces a polyphonic DSP with <num> voices, ready to be used with MIDI events
   -wm8978, -es8388 or -ac101 : to choose codec driver
   Faust options : any option (e.g. -vec -vs 8...). See the Faust compiler documentation.
